profitbooks.net 2018-05-12

# Privacy Policy - ProfitBooks.net

We value our relationship with you and place the highest importance on respecting and protecting your privacy. We want you to feel comfortable and confident when using our product and with entrusting your personal, company and financial information to us.

This privacy statement sets out our current policies and demonstrates our commitment to your financial privacy. We may change the content or services found on our website at any time without notice, and consequently our privacy policy may change at any time in the future. You agree to revisit this page regularly and your continued access to or use of the website will mean that you agree to the changes.

**  
Personal Information**

If you register to use the password-protected portions of the website, we will ask you to provide us with data about yourself (Your name, Email ID and other company conformation). We maintain strict security standards and procedures with a view to preventing unauthorized access to your data by anyone, including our staff. We use various methods like strong data encryption, firewall and server authentication to protect the security of your data. All Group companies, all our staff and whenever we hire third parties to provide support services, we will require them to observe our privacy standards and to allow us to audit them for compliance.

Any personal information received will only be used to fulfill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone.

**  
Third Party Information Sharing**  
We do not share your information with any of the third parties.

**  
Security of your Data**  
We use industry-accepted best methods to protect your information. We review our security procedures carefully and comply with applicable laws and security standards. Your sensitive information, such as credit card information, is sent securely while transacting with Payment Gateway. We do not store your credit card information in our system. Our staff is trained and required to safeguard your information.

Application data is transmitted over a secure https connection with 256-bit encryption.

**  
Cancellation**  
If you wish to cancel the service, your data will be retained on our system for 6 months. You will not be charged during this period. If you chose to activate your account during this period, you can work on the same data. After 6 months, data will be completely deleted from our system. You can export the account data in Excel format anytime as long as your account is active.

**  
Refund policy**  
If you are not satisfied with our services, within 30 days from the purchase date, we will refund the money you have paid us for remaining period of your subscription.
